(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Top 7's fateful semifinal)
(Round 4: Morning at the Airport)
(Officially open for business, featuring frosted windows)
(The battle of kimchi stew)
(Kim Hoon versus Jung Ho Young)
Our food is much more charming.
(Jung Ho Young and Song Hoon)
(Secured a spot in the finals)
(Only two more spots left)
(Who will make it to the finals?)
The promotional materials. We made them pop out.
(Hororok Samgye Soft Tofu)
This time, we went all in at the auction.
(During the auction)
(Starting the bidding with C Restaurant,)
(Ho Yoon made bold investments.)
(C Restaurant: minus 600 dollars)
(Lower display case: minus 240 dollars)
(3 banners: minus 380 dollars)
I went absolutely crazy at the auction all alone.
(Total deducted: 1,220 dollars)
(The most spent among the 7 teams)
It's to attract customers.
(A daring investment to attract customers)
(Spotted the 3 banners right away)
(Kim Ho Yoon's promotional items, 3 banners)
I'd like one of those.
(After checking the banners)
(Ordering immediately)
(Order)
- Okay, one samgye soft tofu.
- All right.
- Mild?
- Yes.
Let's do this.
The menu we prepared is samgye soft tofu.
(Abalone samgye soft tofu)
I wanted the meal to be healthier and heartier.
So I decided to mix samgyetang...
with soft bean curd stew.
"Hororok" gives off the feeling of...
one warm bowl, especially for breakfast.
It's just one bowl,
and it'll fill your body up.
We have abalone samgye soft tofu.
The spicy version is sold at the same price.
The meal is delicious and hearty.
(Abalone samgye soft tofu set, 18.90 dollars)
(Wild chive soy sauce, salted squid and radish salad,)
(thistle rice balls)
The location of the promotional items is...
unbelievable.
(Where all customers pass by)
The electronic billboard and standing sign are...
absolutely overwhelming.
See that, and you're bound to order that menu.
Doesn't Chef Ho Yoon have two promotional items?
He sure does.
(There were already banners next to the kiosk,)
(but he even claimed the front desk display case.)
(Discovered the display case)
(The menu photos are in the display case.)
The chicken and...
- Tofu soup?
- Yes.
Tofu soup.
(1 of Kim Ho Yoon's Hororok Samgye Soft Tofu)
Here it comes. Two samgye soft tofu.
Three samgye soft tofu.
Nice, the orders are coming in.
Good. We're on a roll. Great.
They're on a roll.
Chef Kim Ho Yoon is getting orders.
- Here it is.
- We have another order. Nice.
(The kitchen is buzzing with activity.)
- Please give us a second.
It's being plated right now.
(Orders keep pouring in.)
More squid in that, please.
The menu is bomb.
It couldn't be any better.
Let's tell the customers to dip the rice balls into the soup.
- How generous.
- Is that so?
(Staring)
Chicken drumstick.
- Give me one after business hours.
- Okay.
The chicken drumsticks are huge.
(A foreign customer ordered samgye soft tofu.)
Is this the best airport food we've ever had?
Probably.
I don't know. I've had Taco Bell at the airport, guys.
(Impressed)
- Gosh.
- The chicken is really good.
The best airport food.
This soup is heavenly for me.
Even the tofu is great.
Like, actually great.
(Dancing)
Can I dump this into the soup?
- No.
- Okay, go ahead.
- Okay, fine.
It's making the food nicer.
Mommy is in heaven.
This is so good.
(Heavenly spoonfuls)
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy)
(An order for Jung Ho Young's restaurant)
- It's going off again.
- Oh, gosh.
I thought it was ours. The stew is selling well.
Gosh, everyone is eating Chef Ho Young's food.
Chef Jung Ho Young has always been good.
Either way, that team is unbeatable.
True, he's on another level.
We should just...
Let's at least hold on to second place.
Let's hold on to it.
The kiosks are all occupied.
(More and more people flock to the food court.)
- The kiosks?
- All five are occupied.
(One couple is taking their sweet time deciding.)
(What?)
Which restaurant is that?
Are the fried eggs and instant cup noodles free?
(Spotted something)
(Kim Hoon's promotional item)
"When you order kimchi stew at A restaurant."
Which one is A Restaurant?
Chef's Cooking... Right here.
- Isn't that better?
- This kimchi stew?
(Done with the payment)
Okay. One kimchi stew.
- Okay.
- One kimchi stew.
Don't give up!
It's not over until it's over!
Should I get kimchi stew?
- Tofu set.
- If we order from A Restaurant,
- How about we share?
- those are free.
(Realised)
(Amazed)
You're right. Order kimchi stew from A restaurant,
and dishes like spicy stir-fried pork are free.
If you order from A Restaurant.
- How about we order kimchi stew...
- Okay.
- and get the rest?
(The power of promotional items and freebies)
- One more kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew.
- We're not going home.
- We're going to the finals.
We're going home after selling out.
(Making a resolution with every order)
- Thank you.
- Enjoy. Thank you.
- Thank you. Enjoy.
- Enjoy.
Thank you.
This is amazing.
My gosh, look at the set.
- You also get ramyeon?
- I know, right? Nice.
Incredible.
- Can I try this one?
- It's like...
Go ahead. Try the meat.
(Spicy stir-fried pork)
It's good.
It's really good.
- I want this one.
- Dig in. Is that good?
Katsuobushi meets cucumber.
- Is it good?
- Yes, it is.
This set is very colourful...
- with the many different dishes.
- Who wants the shrimp?
(Tasted the spicy kimchi stew)
(Plenty is the best)
(Perilla oil kimchi stew wins praise for its generous portions.)
(Amazed)
Freebies work.
(1 hour and 30 minutes into business)
How come everyone got that?
With ramyeon, with rice...
They got side dishes with something else.
(A noticeable increase in instant cup noodle customers)
It was either stew or instant cup noodles.
The ratio was about 6 to 4.
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy's share is going back up.)
Just believe that we'll get in second place.
We're in second place.
- Us? We're in 2nd place.
- We're in 2nd place.
Second place.
Nice.
Currently, Kim Hoon and Lee Sung Hoon...
have the same sales.
Unbelievable.
This is nerve-racking.
We're in an emergency state.
An emergency state, for real.
(Good Morning Earth by Lee Sung Hoon)
Nice.
All chefs here seemed like they'd go for Korean food.
Why don't we focus on...
- foreign customers?
- Sure.
(Grilled sandwich)
(Grilled cheese sandwich)
(Grilled egg and cheese sandwich)
(Grilled ham and cheese sandwich)
We prepared sandwiches...
as well as a set with a sandwich included.
(Special set, 22 dollars)
Five white ragu, please.
Next, 1 egg and 1 ham and cheese.
- My gosh.
- One special set.
- Special set.
- Yes.
Hang in there!
Toast.
The customers ordered toast.
All three ordered toast.
Thank you.
(Buzzing with crowds)
My gosh.
Lee Sung Hoon. The sandwich is...
(Surprised)
Goodness.
The sandwich is...
Unexpectedly?
The grilled sandwich is in the second-place range.
- Second place?
- Yes, in the second-place range.
I thought it'd come in last.
Foreign customers may prefer sandwiches,
but will Koreans eat sandwiches before leaving Korea?
I had such a doubt.
But...
Aren't dishes like these heavy?
I remember we'll be served an in-flight meal.
Rice is too heavy for breakfast.
They're all rice.
- I want a sandwich.
- Sandwich?
I should also get something simple.
The sandwich looks the simplest.
When Korean food is for sharing,
a sandwich is a solo meal.
Other teams serve...
hot meals packed in earthen pots.
Some customers want a simple, light breakfast.
With a sandwich, you can have a few bites and take it with you.
It was a great idea.
(A great menu by finding a niche)
- Do you want rice?
- No. Do they have coffee?
I want something to drink.
Have a sandwich.
Okay, sandwich.
(The only menu with drinks included is Lee Sung Hoon's.)
My restaurant used to serve drinks,
so we're the only ones who can sell drinks here.
It's over there.
- We can include drinks in the set.
- That's a good idea.
Drinks are included in both the single menu and set.
"There's also coffee and juice! It's included!"
I focused on the niche.
Do you want orange juice?
I do.
What about you, honey? Coffee?
Let's get coffee after breakfast.
Seven iced coffee.
Coffee is the winning move.
Many people order it.
There's also a seven-dollar menu.
The sandwich is the only menu that's under ten dollars.
- One egg, one ragu.
(Sandwich only and a drink, 7 dollars)
Here you go.
Thank you. Enjoy.
It seemed like the other restaurants were a little pricey.
(Spring beef soup meal by Choi Sang Hyun, 19 dollars)
(Pho meal by Hong Seok Cheon, 17.90 dollars)
(The other restaurants only have set meals that are quite pricey.)
We did have a set menu,
but we also added a stand alone menu item...
with an unbeatable price advantage.
The sandwiches by Good Morning Earth.
The prices are great.
- Seven dollars.
- People could order one each.
Seven dollars.
(They also offer reasonably priced side dishes,)
(giving customers a diverse and satisfying selection...)
(at a low price.)
(Winning over even Korean customers,)
(the strategy of selling more at lower margins is paying off.)
- Tae Hee, as we expected, - Yes?
there are customers...
- Of course.
- who enjoy light breakfasts.
- It's not bad, is it?
- No.
We're doing well.
- Let's step it up.
- Okay.
(The niche strategist Lee Sung Hoon)
Chef Sung Hoon is amazing.
He's a real strategist, isn't he?
Selling sandwiches...
Even thinking about it, and what's more,
it's selling, which is a shocker.
That's so cool.
(Seok Cheon came to spy on Lee Sung Hoon's kitchen.)
You seem backed up with orders.
No.
- Have a pleasant trip.
- The orders keep coming in.
(Tied for 2nd place, Kim Hoon also spied on them.)
Amazing.
(Jealous)
Unbelievable.
You're on a roll, Chef.
I'm jealous.
Are you selling well?
(Everyone comes out to watch as the battle for 2nd place heats up.)
It's my first visit.
(Even the 1st-place team is just as curious about their secret.)
- Hi.
- What is that?
I looked around.
When we sold 90-something,
that team already had 83 to 84 orders.
They were really busy.
(Currently in a fierce battle for 2nd place)
(Lee Sung Hoon's sales: 606 dollars)
(Kim Hoon's sales: 606 dollars)
You also get an instant cup noodle. Hold on a second.
One egg.
(Lee Sung Hoon's sales: 614 dollars, Kim Hoon's sales: 623 dollars)
(Kim Hoon's sales: 640 dollars)
- Thank you. Have a nice day.
- Thank you. You too.
(Lee Sung Hoon's sales: 636 dollars)
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Enjoy your meal.
(With the battle for 2nd place neck and neck)
(30 minutes passed since they reached the same sales total)
Currently, Kim Hoon...
- What is it this time?
- and Lee Sung Hoon...
have...
a 140-dollar sales difference.
(The battle for 2nd place is starting to see a clear gap.)
Currently, in second place in sales is...
I don't want to go home. Please.
I'm dead anxious.
(Kim Hoon, Lee Sung Hoon)
(Who's currently in 2nd place in sales?)
Lee Sung Hoon.
(Current 2nd place: Lee Sung Hoon)
Let's go.
(Lee Sung Hoon's sales: 895 dollars)
(Sales update)
(Chef's Cooking Makes Us Happy: 755 dollars)
(Eat And Flight: 1,700 dollars)
(Good Morning Earth: 895 dollars)
Lee Sung Hoon.
No way.
We lost second place.
Cool.
(8am, 2 hours into business)
(One change as 8am rolls out)
(Foreigner)
(A noticeable increase in international customers)
(And then, one after another)
(Selecting Japanese)
(The peak departure hour at Incheon Airport)
(8am)
(At Terminal 2, today's stage,)
(the busiest time for departing flights is between 7am and 9am.)
(When international passengers heading home begin to flood in)
(Foreign customers, Korean customers)
(Foreign customers now make up more than 60 percent of all customers.)
Korean beef soup set.
(There are more foreigners than Koreans now.)
(How will this shift the menu preferences?)
(A Chinese-speaking customer walks in.)
(Lee Yeon Bok's eye-catching sign, auctioned for 250 dollars)
(The Masked Noodle King)
(Premium Chinese cuisine made with care and flavour)
(Walking straight to the kiosk)
(Selecting Chinese)
(Selecting Lee Yeon Bok's restaurant)
(Ordering Chinese-style naengmyeon)
(Another Chinese-speaking customer is looking at the display.)
- Do you want a receipt?
- I want to order...
the menu in the display board.
- Just a moment, sir.
- Okay.
Can I have 1 naengmyeon and 1 jjamppong?
Thank you.
(Ordered two dishes just from Yeon Bok's)
(Order)
- Here it is. Naengmyeon.
- Naengmyeon.
- One naengmyeon.
- Okay.
One naengmyeon.
(Another order)
(Orders from foreign customers start coming in.)
- One jjamppong.
(Naengmyeon noodles are rinsed in cold water.)
(A generous amount of broth topped with icy flakes)
Good. Be generous.
(Topped with plenty of vegetables and seafood)
(A generous serving of samseon Chinese-style naengmyeon)
Okay, here's your order. You ordered naengmyeon, right?
- Good, thank you.
- Enjoy.
(Stopping)
(The customer suddenly shows his order slip.)
What's your order number?
Right. Just a moment.
- Are you Chinese?
- Yes, I am.
Did you order naengmyeon or something else?
I ordered one naengmyeon and a bottle of water.
I see.
(Responding in Chinese right away)
He also ordered water.
I still have to wait for my water, right?
(Informing the customer to get the water from the counter)
- Hi.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
By any chance, do you have a small bowl?
- What?
- A small bowl?
She needs a small bowl.
- Is this small enough?
- Yes, may I get two?
Two? Of course.
One more, please.
- Thank you.
- This one?
- Yes.
(Lee Yeon Bok's sales: 480.60 dollars)
- This one. Thank you.
- This one.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
There are barely any Koreans.
- Was it a foreigner just now?
- Yes, it was a foreigner.
(And then, an unexpected variable emerges.)
Starting now, the real-time customer ratings...
are available for ordering customers.
(Revealing the customer ratings in real time)
Customers can check...
the ratings next to the kiosk.
(The customer ratings display)
(Turning)
It must be the real-time customer ratings.
(Changing restaurants after checking the ratings)
(A display is also installed at the entrance to the food court.)
(Now, the customers' eyes are on the ratings.)
Lee Sung Hoon.
(2nd in sales: Lee Sung Hoon)
Four stars.
I can't believe it.
Kim Hoon.
(3rd in sales: Kim Hoon)
Four point one stars.
Why is it so low?
Lee Yeon Bok.
(4th in sales: Lee Yeon Bok)
Four point four stars.
We're doing great.
(2nd in sales: Kim Hoon, 3rd in sales: Lee Sung Hoon)
(Lee Yeon Bok has a higher rating.)
Customers might not order from places with low ratings.
(Higher ratings have become a major advantage.)
(What they will do to counter the revealed ratings)
Right.
- Give two abalones starting now.
- Okay.
- Now it's a battle for ratings.
- Two abalones.
To bump up the quality of the dish.
We originally served one abalone.
(One whole abalone originally)
We started serving two abalones from then on.
- This is jjamppong, right?
- Yes, it's jjamppong.
My gosh, look at the abalones.
(2 abalones)
(How will the customers rate it?)
(Delivering the jjamppong)
Is this my jjamppong?
Is the quality for real?
(The visuals get a pass.)
(Samseon jjamppong with 2 abalones)
(Impressed)
The abalone is great.
(Samseon jjamppong with 2 abalones)
There are two big ones in here.
(Another customer ordered Chinese-style naengmyeon)
Look at how plump the abalones are.
(Chinese-style naengmyeon: It had plenty of abalone,)
(and I liked that it was the only cold dish.)
(Thanks to that, Yeon Bok's ratings...)
(15 minutes later)
(Went up)
Currently, in second place in customer ratings is Lee Yeon Bok.
The tablet must be showing the real-time ratings.
You're right.
(After checking the ratings display)
(Picked The Masked Noodle King)
(Order)
That's it.
- One naengmyeon.
Okay, let's go.
(Order)
What is it? Read it out quickly.
(A storm of orders)
It has begun.
- Five here are done.
- Okay.
Starting from here, one naengmyeon. Two.
We need to serve ten starting now.
- Ten?
- Yes.
Oh, my.
Currently, Kim Hoon and Lee Yeon Bok are...
battling for third place,
with only a 100-dollar difference in sales.
Okay, we're battling for the better place.
- Serve quickly.
- Understood.
With only a 100-dollar difference...
- in sales.
- Oh, no.
- Chef Lee Yeon Bok.
- Chef Lee Yeon Bok is good.
Chef Lee Yeon Bok is scary.
He's good.
(1st place: Kim Hoon)
(2nd place: Kim Hoon)
(3rd place: Kim Hoon)
(Kim Hoon has gone down to 3rd place from 1st.)
(And now, he's being chased by Lee Yeon Bok.)
Will we lose?
Let's secure 3rd place. We can't go down to 4th place.
We must defend third place at all costs.
(Fall any further, and he's out.)
Let's think of the variables.
Here.
We're in third place.
Chef Lee Yeon Bok is in fourth.
- Our sales must be similar.
- Right?
Yes.
The rent was 400 dollars.
(Kim Hoon's auction cost: 400 dollars on rent)
The promotional fee was 320 dollars, so we used a total of 720 dollars.
Chef Lee Yeon Bok's rent was ten dollars,
and his promotional fee was 250 dollars.
(Lee Yeon Bok's auction cost: 260 dollars total)
Once we factored that in too, we were at a disadvantage.
(Kim Hoon: 720 dollars, Lee Yeon Bok: 260 dollars)
(In a disadvantage by 460 dollars)
Variable number one.
- The ingredient cost...
- If he used a lot.
being 2,000 dollars.
Our ingredient costs have not been disclosed yet.
- So we can't be sure.
- Is that so?
This is tough. I think 2,000 dollars is too much.
We currently used 1,000 dollars.
It's a favourable variable.
Didn't Chef Lee Yeon Bok say he prepared plenty?
I feel like we used the most on ingredient cost.
Let's say it was 1,500 dollars. It'd be 1,740 dollars.
Only if his ingredient cost is over 1,500 dollars.
- It has to be over 1,500 dollars.
- Over?
(Estimated ingredient cost)
(Around 1,500 dollars, Around 1,000 dollars)
(Favourable by 500 dollars)
Let's say we win. Then...
(Estimated to be 40 dollars ahead)
Variable number 2, the last 1, was the customer ratings.
Let's wait. It's too early to give up.
- If only we'd get a rush of orders.
- Right? Please.
(Sighing)
The CEO of Dookki.
He said he dreamed of me advancing to the finals.
(As the battle for 3rd place unfolds)
Orders will close...
- in ten minutes.
- No, please.
Give us one last push.
(The current sales of the two restaurants are...)
(Kim Hoon: 1,175 dollars, Yeon Bok: 1,085.80 dollars)
(A 90 dollar difference)
- One kimchi stew.
- Kimchi stew.
(17 dollars)
(The difference became 110 dollars.)
Nice. The last push.
Currently, Kim Hoon and Lee Yeon Bok have...
a 110-dollar sales difference again.
(Order)
- What is it?
- Another naengmyeon.
- One naengmyeon.
- Okay.
(Another order)
What?
- One naengmyeon.
- Okay.
(Naengmyeon orders in a row: 35.60 dollars)
(Order)
- What is it?
- Another naengmyeon.
- Okay.
Now that it's getting hotter,
naengmyeon is selling well.
(As it gets past 9am, it starts getting hotter.)
Choose three.
- How about naengmyeon?
- Naengmyeon?
- I want something cold.
- It says it's the best menu.
Being the best menu is important.
- One naengmyeon.
Currently, Kim Hoon and Lee Yeon Bok have...
just a five-dollar sales difference.
Just a five-dollar sales difference.
(The gap narrows in an instant.)
Please, just one push.
(Kim Hoon is at risk of dropping to 4th place.)
- Yes!
- Kimchi stew.
(Order)
(Kim Hoon pulls ahead again.)
- Gimbap.
(However, the chase continues.)
(Order)
What is it this time?
- Another naengmyeon.
Yes.
(Order)
- Another jjamppong.
It's that one. The Masked Evil King.
(Picked The Masked Noodle King)
(Checking the customer ratings while ordering)
(Turning)
The Masked Noodle King.
(Picked The Masked Noodle King)
Four more orders need to be served.
- What?
- Four more orders.
What's this?
Suddenly.
- What's going on?
- I'll clean this up later.
Currently, Kim Hoon and Lee Yeon Bok have...
just a 19.80-dollar...
- sales difference.
- Gosh.
- A 19.80-dollar difference?
- Business...
will close shortly.
(Almost a one-bowl difference)
Gosh.
- Oh, no.
- Gimbap.
Let's get selling.
(1 minute before business hours end)
(What would the last customers choose?)
(Is it Lee Yeon Bok's or Kim Hoon's?)
Morning at the Airport. Orders are now closed.
(Business has ended.)
I'm really curious.
It's hard to guess, right? It was a nip-and-tuck match.
Of course.
We auctioned some stuff and such.
Round Four of Street Restaurant Fighter.
Here are the results.
Only the top 3 teams among the 7...
with the highest net profit after deducting...
sales-related costs, auction costs, and ingredient costs...
will advance to the final round.
First, here's the sales ranking...
of the seven restaurants.
See? The rankings will be announced first.
(Sales ranking)
(1st: Jung Ho Young, 2,793.56 dollars)
(5th: Kim Ho Yoon, 1,203.05 dollars)
(6th: Hong Seok Cheon, 754.79 dollars)
(7th: Choi Sang Hyun, 511.86 dollars)
We're in sixth?
(1st, 5th, 6th, 7th in sales)
(And)
Fourth place, Lee Yeon Bok.
(4th: Lee Yeon Bok, 1,376.05 dollars)
Third, Kim Hoon.
(3rd: Kim Hoon, 1,397.37 dollars, About a 20-dollar difference)
Second place, Lee Sung Hoon.
(2nd: Lee Sung Hoon, 1,539.09 dollars)
(Sales ranking, 1st: Jung Ho Young,)
(2nd: Lee Sung Hoon, 3rd: Kim Hoon, 4th: Lee Yeon Bok,)
(5th: Kim Ho Yoon, 6th: Hong Seok Cheon, 7th: Choi Sang Hyun)
Now, here are the sales...
with the customer ratings reflected.
This is what matters.
- Will the order change?
- Maybe.
The average.
His customer ratings were high.
(Chef Yeon Bok)
(Sales ranking)
(1st: Jung Ho Young, 4.14, 3,589.72 dollars)
Fourth place.
Fourth place, Kim Hoon.
(4th: Kim Hoon)
It's 4.31 stars.
We went down.
(Dropped to 4th from 3rd place)
In the sales ranking, we were in third place.
I thought we were safe because we were above the cut off line.
But with the customer ratings, we dropped to fourth.
(4th: Kim Hoon, 4.31, 1,855 dollars)
Oh, no.
- We lost in customer ratings.
- This is bad.
- Third?
- You might make it to second place.
(Sighing)
We need a minimum of four stars.
Third place.
Lee Yeon Bok.
Four point five stars.
Total sales are 1,892.06 dollars.
That's so close.
Only a 40-dollar difference?
(37.06-dollar difference with 4th place Kim Hoon)
Second place, Lee Sung Hoon.
- Four point one stars.
- Four point one?
(2nd place: Lee Sung Hoon, 4.1 stars)
Well done.
Thank you.
Good job.
(Sales ranking)
Everyone's rankings are in the fours.
Next, here are the rankings after deducting rent...
- and promotional costs.
- We're in last place.
(The chef with the highest promotional spending)
Fourth place, Kim Hoon.
(4th: Kim Hoon, 720 dollars, 1,135 dollars)
Total sales are 1,135 dollars.
- What a bummer.
- It's a real bummer.
The promotional items were...
We should've spent less.
Third place, Lee Sung Hoon.
Total sales are 1,562.34 dollars.
Good job.
My heart is pounding hard. It won't end.
Look at the huge difference.
Second place, Lee Yeon Bok.
Total sales are 1,632.06 dollars.
(He moves up to 2nd place with 69.72-dollar difference.)
Yeon Bok is in second place!
He went up.
They must have been in 1st, 2nd, and 3rd.
(Sales ranking)
(1st: Jung Ho Young, 2nd: Lee Yeon Bok,)
(3rd: Lee Sung Hoon, 4th: Kim Hoon,)
(5th: Hong Seok Cheon, 6th: Kim Ho Yoon,)
(7th: Choi Sang Hyun)
All that's left is the ingredient costs.
(Only the ingredient cost deduction is left.)
Next, here are the final sales rankings...
- The final rankings.
- after deducting...
the ingredient costs.
Be quiet.
The ingredient costs.
(All teams ordered their ingredients through the same ordering system.)
(The ingredient costs...)
(remain confidential from one another...)
(until the end of the business.)
We won't know how much we each used.
The ingredient cost may be the variable.
Seventh place.
Choi Sang Hyun.
(Final 7th place: Choi Sang Hyun)
Sixth place, Kim Ho Yoon.
(Final 6th place: Kim Ho Yoon)
(Final 5th place)
Fifth place, Hong Seok Cheon.
The restaurants will close.
(Closure confirmed)
Next, here is the final first-place restaurant...
of Morning at the Airport.
We clearly know who is in first place.
- First place, Jung Ho Young.
- It's Ho Young.
(1st place: Jung Ho Young and Song Hoon)
The final total sales are 2,190.92 dollars.
(1st place: Jung Ho Young)
- Here.
- Congratulations.
That's absolutely overwhelming.
Amazing.
With the most sales, survival is secured.
- Congratulations.
(1st place Jung Ho Young advances to the finals.)
Coming in first place obviously makes me happy.
Absolutely.
There's only one more win left.
Since we've come this far,
I'll do my best until the end to win.
(Only 2 survival spots remain.)
Please.
Please, Father.
Kim Hoon.
Lee Sung Hoon.
Lee Yeon Bok.
Out of the remaining three restaurants,
only two can advance to the finals.
(Only 2 teams can make it to the finals.)
Here's the restaurant in second place that has secured survival.
- Second place?
With second place, won't we get a broad idea?
(Current rankings)
(2nd: Lee Yeon Bok, 3rd: Lee Sung Hoon, 4th: Kim Hoon)
Second place.
(Final 2nd place)
Lee Sung Hoon.
The final total sales are 695.60 dollars.
(2nd place: Lee Sung Hoon)
(Total sales: 695.60 dollars)
Thank you.
Congratulations. How cool.
Lee Sung Hoon, survival is secured.
(2nd place Lee Sung Hoon advances to the finals.)
Congratulations.
Amazing.
Let's go.
We always advanced with results that were so close.
When being announced second place,
it felt like a reward for all the hard work.
It was worthwhile and delightful.
The remaining restaurants are Kim Hoon's...
and Lee Yeon Bok's.
Let's see.
Just until now, the two restaurants...
were 497.06 dollars apart in sales.
- That's quite apart.
- Lee Yeon Bok was in the lead.
The sales.
(Yeon Bok is in the lead.)
How much did Kim Hoon use in ingredients?
Please, Father.
If Chef Lee Yeon Bok used less than 1,500 dollars...
(Kim Hoon kept calculating the ingredient cost variables.)
I heard Chef Lee used a lot on ingredients.
He used 2,000 dollars.
- Two thousand dollars?
- No way.
I should've spent much less on the ingredients.
(Current sales)
(Kim Hoon: 1,135 dollars, Lee Yeon Bok: 1,632.06 dollars)
Here's the restaurant...
in third place that has secured survival.
Third place.
(Who will come in final 3rd place?)
With the final sales...
My heart is pounding.
Please.
I'm all scared even though I got eliminated.
I can't watch it. It's hurting me.
So this is how it feels.
With the final sales...
(Kim Hoon's final sales, Lee Yeon Bok's final sales)
coming to 175.67 dollars,
(Kim Hoon's final sales: 175.67 dollars)
(Lee Yeon Bok's final sales: 165.62 dollars)
Kim Hoon's survival is secured.
(Final 3rd place Kim Hoon advances to the finals.)
- Thank you.
- Well done.
- You did well.
- Thank you.
Good job.
(Overtook Lee Yeon Bok on ingredient costs)
- Unbelievable.
- Really.
Seriously.
Honestly,
I didn't know we'd come this far.
Even so, I kept telling myself that we could do it.
- We must win.
- Yes. "We must win."
To be frank...
I'm suddenly tearing up.
I can't do it.
I can't get the words out. I can't.
Here's what crossed my mind.
You come to an age where you realise...
how far you can go.
In your 20s, you dream ambitiously.
In your 30s, you slowly realise your limits.
But in this survival show,
I kept telling myself that we could do it...
and didn't set a limit for myself.
I'm so going to win.
(Words like self-hypnosis,)
(keeping him from setting limits on himself)
I must've put a limit on myself until now.
I want to prove myself...
with a good result.
(Final 4th place: Lee Yeon Bok)
Oh, dear.
Oh, my.
Lee Yeon Bok. Ingredient costs were 1,466.44 dollars.
- They were 1,466.44 dollars.
- What?
They used 1,460 dollars?
Lee Yeon Bok's final sales were...
just 10.05 dollars lower than Kim Hoon's.
(10.05-dollar difference with Kim Hoon)
No way.
Ten dollars and five cents.
(Sighing)
All sorts of thoughts went through my head.
Because we always sold out fast,
we wanted to sell as much as possible this time.
(During Round 1)
We'll be out of mianbao xia in no time.
(Ingredient shortage crisis in Round 1)
This is bad. I wonder if we can serve all the orders.
We can serve about ten more orders.
These won't make ten servings.
(Sold out early in Round 2)
In food courts, a lot of people swarm in.
If I sell about 300 servings, I'll win for sure.
I should've spent less on buying ingredients.
(He didn't get as many orders as he'd hoped.)
With the difference of 10.05 dollars,
your business will be closed down.
- It's 10.05 dollars?
- Just 1 more naengmyeon...
You're right. If I had sold just one more naengmyeon...
It was such a pity.
Our fate has already been decided, so it can't be helped.
But it was such a pity.
I've been on many survival shows,
but Street Restaurant Fighter...
As I advanced each level, it was so much fun.
It's funny even as I make jjamppong.
I can't believe one order of jjamppong and mianbao xia...
makes me so happy.
- It was so interesting.
- It's well-boiled.
"What topic awaits me next?"
"What kind of style should I go for?"
I wonder what the mission is now.
I've been doing business for over ten years,
but never a business like this.
(It's not just you. It's the first for me as well.)
I had so much fun until here.
Although I got eliminated in the semifinals,
I look forward to what will come next.
(Goodbye)
As the only contestant who's taken part in every single mission,
it's such a shame that I need to leave...
without doing one last mission.
(Hororok Samgye Soft Tofu)
I got the confidence to improve through this.
(Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in 5 Minutes)
I got to watch the chefs...
and grow from it.
I was very proud to be here,
and I made many good memories with Seung Jae.
So I'll leave happily.
Personally, I've had so much fun here.
Itaewon Class again...
I stayed away from the restaurant business for a while,
but through this show,
I started thinking, "Should I get back to it?"
I felt the urge come over me.
- You've done enough business.
- What?
- Exactly.
For the first time in a while,
I got this thrilling rush of dopamine.
As I got to feel that...
"I really like doing business. I love it."
That was what I thought.
(Itaewon Class Thai)
(Spring Beef Bone Soup Ready in 5 Minutes)
(Hororok Samgye Soft Tofu)
(The Masked Noodle King)
The three restaurants that have survived...
Round Four, Morning at the Airport. Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- We're back to being enemies.
The current total of the prize money...
is 181,047.46 dollars.
The amount is within my reach now.
You are left with...
just one more business.
The final one.
What is it going to be?
The customers of the final mission...
(The final customers the 3 teams will serve)
- This is very important.
- They're university students.
University students?
(University students)
(The final round will be around universities?)
Foreigners.
University students and foreigners?
International university students.
(International university students?)
Is there a foreign language university?
- Seniors.
- What?
Office workers.
What's this?
Families with children.
And restaurant industry workers.
- All of them.
- All of them are customers.
Street Restaurant Fighter.
- Will it be in a mall?
- The final mission is...
Everyone's Restaurant.
Isn't it a restaurant which can satisfy everyone?
That's what I'd expect for the final mission.
A restaurant to satisfy everyone.
You must complete Everyone's Restaurant...
which will satisfy all the different groups.
This is harder, actually.
For the final round's restaurant,
six of the initial booths are linked to form one big booth.
It will be run like an actual restaurant.
- I see.
- One booth is for the kitchen,
and the other five are the dining areas.
- Like an actual restaurant.
- It's an indoor restaurant.
It's a store.
You must design the new signboard...
and the interior of the restaurant yourself.
(They must design the signboard and the interior themselves too.)
You can buy however many four-persons tables for your booth.
Each table costs 40 dollars.
It'll be deducted from the total revenue.
We need to pay for the tables too?
We need to think about how many tables to buy.
Also, you can hire part-timers.
For each part-timer,
the labour cost of 200 dollars will be deducted.
At least we didn't need to clear the tables, serve,
- or manage the register.
- Exactly.
But this time, we need to do all that.
This round will be a blind evaluation.
The business area of the final round will be revealed.
(Which business area will Everyone's Restaurant be at?)
(Where is the final business area...)
(where the winner will be decided?)
(Western inland region)
(The capital of flavours, Jeonju)
(Korea's first culinary mecca chosen by the UNESCO)
(Selected as the Creative City of Gastronomy by UNESCO in 2012)
(Traditional and modern food coexist.)
(The final battle ground: Jeonju Hanok Village)
I hope it works out.
It was a struggle to come here.
We made it this far.
Tonight...
(Jung Ho Young and Song Hoon)
I hope we go home smiling.
I think this is the last chance...
I can work with Chef Song Hoon like this.
(The best Japanese cuisine chef and Western cuisine chef)
You can't come here, Song Hoon.
- It's you two?
- Yes.
(Everyone was wary of the two skilled chefs.)
(What the two chefs prioritised)
Firstly, it has to taste good.
I must make sure it tastes good.
But isn't that being what we are? Being like chefs.
(With the obsession for taste,)
(the formidable chefs have made it to the finals.)
Actually, just once...
I want to reach the peak.
It's finally the last round.
It's really the last dance.
Since we've made it this far, we must win.
(Kim Hoon and Kim Jong In)
I'm starting to feel nervous.
Our strength is data, actually.
(Kim Hoon's strategy was clear from Round 1.)
I believe data doesn't lie.
(Round 1 data: Office district and steak rice bowl)
(Round 2 data)
(Beer festival and sweet fried chicken)
(Round 3 data)
(Amusement park and dessert set)
(Round 4 data: Airport and kimchi stew)
(The data has proven it already.)
(The risk-taker has overcome all the business areas with data.)
(The data gambler)
I fight based on the data.
Chef Lee Sung Hoon's team...
is always a dark horse.
(Lee Sung Hoon and Yu Tae Hee)
(During the first appearance)
Who is it?
- Who is he?
- I don't know.
(From an underdog that nobody knew...)
(to advance to the final)
(They even beat the boss of Busan.)
The final survivor is...
Lee Sung Hoon.
(He even beat Seven-star chef Edward Kwon.)
(The dark horse showcased various genres of food.)
Since I made it to the finals, I'll give it my everything...
and win no matter what.
(Underdog Chef, Lee Sung Hoon, Culinary Chef, Jung Ho Young,)
(Data Strategist, Kim Hoon)
The day of the showdown.
(Their last time heading to the battlefield)
- This is the last day.
- It's the last day.
Here we are.
- Finally.
- It's nice.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
(Final Round's Street Arena)
(Three restaurants are set up for the final round.)
It looked like an actual store. It looked grand too.
We were always given a food court-sized space,
but now, it's become a restaurant which is six times bigger.
(Gimpo logistics warehouse, 4:30am)
(The booths head to Jeonju.)
(Gimpo to Jeonju: 265km)
(The booths have arrived after a 3-hour drive.)
(The restaurant was built by linking 6 booths.)
(From a booth which only housed kitchen,)
(it transformed into a restaurant with a dining area.)
It felt like I actually opened a restaurant.
It's the first time with a dining area.
"Can we really serve customers here?"
I felt myself tremble.
Street Restaurant Fighter.
Welcome to its final round.
It's the final round.
First, please reveal your Everyone's Restaurant.
One, two, three.
(Noodle Shop of Brothers with Different-sized Stomachs)
We are Noodle Shop of Brothers with Different-sized Stomachs.
We're very close like brothers,
but we have different stomach sizes.
We added it in for fun.
The menu we prepared...
is house-made udon noodles.
This is the final round.
It'll be great if I win.
Even if I lose, I want to do something I'm best at.
(Today's noodles: Super chewy. Soup: Rich. Chefs: Confident.)
(Noodle Shop of Brothers with Different-sized Stomachs)
(The house-made noodle brothers' confident dining area)
- They have shaved ice too.
- What's this?
They have this too.
(Tabletop menu)
This is the bar table.
You put 4, no, 5 bar tables?
They cost 20 dollars each.
Tables cost a lot.
(Labour cost of 400 dollars deducted)
(Part-timers: Park Su Yeob and Song Seong Jun)
They look powerful.
(Can the house-made noodle brothers satisfy everyone?)
He brought his strongest weapon.
Chef Ho Young is doing udon.
Two, three.
(Lee Sung Hoon and Yu Tae Hee's Everyone's Restaurant revealed)
- Nice.
- "Son of Jeonju."
"Son of Jeonju."
- Are you really from Jeonju?
- Yes.
I was born and raised in Jeonju.
So I named it "Son of Jeonju."
(His shop name shows his overflowing pride in Jeonju.)
We prepared a course menu.
With seven courses,
the price is 34 dollars per head.
(Surprised)
Thirty-four dollars? That's amazing.
That's too strong.
I wanted them to try as many good dishes...
as they could at a reasonable price by making it a course meal.
(7 course menu, 34 dollars)
As for the interior design,
I went with modern Korean and hanok vibe.
My gosh.
- The floor is different.
- That's so cool.
- Yes.
- Very Jeonju-like.
The floor is so pretty.
Six, seven, eight, nine.
- Nine tables here too.
- It feels cosy.
That's really nice.
(Labour cost of 400 dollars deducted)
(Part-timers: Jo Seong Min and Yu Seung Ah)
I wanted to serve them with the mindset...
of repaying the debt to my fellow Jeonju people.
So I named the course meal "Repayment."
You could get around 10 teams in 1 hour.
(Laughing)
- That's your gamble.
- Yes.
If he gets 15 groups,
that's already 500 dollars.
(The gambler made a bold move with the course menu.)
Paying 34 dollars for a 7-course meal is great.
It is, but people might not go because it's expensive.
- I think they will.
- One, two, three.
What?
(Kim Hoon and Kim Jong In's Everyone's Restaurant revealed)
"Seoul Jumbo Pork Cutlet and Hamburger Steak."
We're selling jumbo pork cutlet and hamburger steak.
When I was young, my family would often eat out...
pork cutlet and hamburger steak.
What moves the customers are the dishes...
that bring back memories rather than something surprising.
This time, I wanted to share my memories with Jeonju people,
so I chose pork cutlet and hamburger steak.
It looks like you moved a restaurant from Seoul to here.
Right from Yongsan.
- The Yongsan restaurant.
- Yongsan.
- It's pretty.
- What's this?
Didn't you use it in the previous round?
Yes. I brought what I use in my shop.
(Today, soft ice cream is free.)
- How did you bring this?
- What's this?
- This...
- I can line up hamburger steaks...
- and take them out straight.
- Is it an oven?
It's already all arranged here.
(Part-timer: Park Cheol)
(Labour cost of 200 dollars deducted, the only team with 1 part-timer)
The final mission in Jeonju...
will deduct the table cost, labour cost,
and ingredient costs.
Only one team with the highest revenue...
will become the honorary victor.
(Street Restaurant Fighter)
For the average customer ratings of five stars,
two hundred percent of total sales will be calculated.
- Isn't five stars impossible?
- Right.
For 4 stars, 150 percent of total sales will be calculated.
(Customer rating and sales calculation)
For 1 star, 0 percent of the total sales...
will be calculated...
as the final sales.
That's zero dollars.
If you get one star, it'll be as if you've done nothing.
To check the customer satisfaction, the real-time ratings...
will be displayed in front of your restaurant.
This is how it shows?
This might deter the customers from coming in.
Right.
Jeolla Province, where the final round takes place,
has abundant ingredients.
The specialty of North Jeolla Province, Jangsu Apple,
Jinan Plateau's bracken, dried radish greens,
and shiitake mushrooms.
You must choose one ingredient and make use of it.
(They must make use of North Jeolla Province specialties.)
We chose shiitake mushrooms.
We chose bracken.
- We chose shiitake mushrooms.
- What?
They chose the same.
Please start getting ready...
to open Everyone's Restaurant.
- Good luck.
- You can do it. Good luck!
- All the best.
- Don't get hurt.
Good luck.
(They start preparing for the final round's business.)
Let's do the cheer before we start.
- Here. Different-sized Stomachs.
- Different-sized Stomachs.
- Let's go!
- We got it.
- Let's go.
Make pasta noodles in one hour.
Noodles.
This is the final round.
I decided to do...
what I'm best at and what I can most confidently make.
Since we're Hohyunghojae, which means "brothers,"
our concept is Noodle Shop of Brothers.
Cold udon.
Bibim udon.
Fresh pasta.
(They can choose various noodle dishes.)
- With noodles.
- Which everyone likes.
I'm currently running an udon restaurant.
I'll use house-made udon noodles.
Boil the noodles for four minutes,
and wash them in cold water so it becomes chewy and bouncy.
Give it a cold shower.
Okay.
Place two shrimps.
(Handmade broth)
(Noodle dish 1: Cold udon with bouncy noodles)
Chef Song Hoon will make fresh pasta noodles.
(He brought his own noodle maker.)
I'm making pasta.
(Dough aged for a day)
(Roll it out thinly with a rolling pin.)
(One more time with the noodle maker)
The dough is perfect.
(It's already become this long and thin.)
This is...
already 3m.
(The dough is reborn as noodles.)
I'll use handmade fresh pasta.
Stir-fry calamari and shrimps in olive oil.
Boil the noodles...
and simmer it down in the stock.
It's calamari shrimp fresh pasta.
(Calamari shrimp fresh pasta, 18.50 dollars)
You can have Japanese and Western on one table.
That's the kind of restaurant we wanted to make.
(We prepared everything!)
And...
we'll attract customers with red bean shaved ice.
We came up with the strategy.
The weather is perfect for shaved ice.
Nine was the maximum number of tables we could fit in.
I prepared a lot of small things in detail.
(Song Hoon is in charge of the dining area.)
(Setting the spoon holders)
(Setting the tissues)
(Setting soy sauce)
(The dining area is ready.)
Since we're here already, let's give it a bit more push.
Just once.
Please, just once.
Let's enjoy.
(Noodle Shop of Brothers with Different-sized Stomachs)
(Son of Jeonju)
When you manage the dining area...
Our concept is a course menu.
So I didn't place as many tables as the other restaurants.
Some groups might be in 2, some might be in 4.
Please make suitable seating arrangements.
(Sung Hoon's restaurant will serve a course meal.)
(The seats are spacious.)
I wanted to reduce the tables...
and improve the service on the dining area.
We'll have a lower turnover rate compared to the other teams,
but we have the advantage in the unit cost.
(The average price is about 17 dollars per person.)
(Almost double the other restaurants)
Jeonju's food trend changes very quickly.
They like sensational stuff, both young and old.
Jeonju is known for bibim dishes.
I really didn't want to do bibimbap.
Instead...
(Japanese, Chinese, Korean, Western)
Since I run Japanese, Chinese, Korean, and Western restaurants,
I'll mix them into the course menu.
(Western, Korean, Western, Western, Japanese, Korean, Western)
(Multinational course meal)
The course starts with beef tartare and menchi katsu.
Next is perilla oil makguksu...
and pork tenderloin steak.
Korean melon salad, bracken hangover soup,
and it ends with buckwheat crepe tiramisu.
However,
they do take a lot of effort to cook.
(They do take a lot of effort to cook.)
(For menchi katsu, they need to knead it 1 by 1.)
(Coat it in flour, egg, and breadcrumbs.)
(Deep-fry them 1 by 1.)
(Even the salad dressing is made from scratch using Korean melon.)
(Grilling the tenderloin piece by piece over charcoal)
(18 prep steps for meats and vegetables)
(Prepping cucumbers, Korean melons, cabbage, corn, beets, red onions)
(Chopping onions, prepping sorrel and perilla leaves, and such)
(10 sauces and bases)
(Making button mushroom paste, jalapeno mayo sauce, makguksu soup,)
(perilla oil sauce, perilla pesto, peanut butter sauce, and such)
(8 steps for cooking and desserts)
(Deep-frying menchi katsu, stripping meat from pork spine)
(Cooking buckwheat noodles, hangover soup, and such)
We chose bracken...
as the local specialty of Jeonju.
We are going to make bracken hangover soup using bracken.
(Boil the pork spine to pick off all the lean meat,)
(blanch the bracken,)
(blend it finely,)
(and stir it into the broth.)
(And bracken hangover soup is done.)
I tried to stick strictly to the book...
from prepping to cooking.
Even during the mission where I made tendon,
a lot of chefs asked me why I was doing things so by the book...
instead of hurrying it along.
- I have a question.
- Yes.
(And again, in the finals)
Do the dishes come out 1 by 1 as a course meal?
This time as well, they were like, "Will that even work?"
"Can a course meal really work when this is a competition?"
I thought, "Why are they taking unreasonable risks again?"
If the target audience is foreigners and Gen Z,
I think they would find 34 dollars burdensome.
If it were for families, I think they wouldn't eat it.
I don't think it fits any customer target audience.
Can it deliver 34 dollars' worth of satisfaction here?
(Satisfaction needs to be as high as the steep price point.)
We kind of took a gamble.
It might be all or nothing, but we chose a course meal.
It's all or nothing anyway, since it's the finals.
Those young guys are impressive.
We will prepare diligently,
and we'll try to pull it off steadily and quietly.
(Will their gamble end up all or nothing?)
(Son of Jeonju)
- Are you nervous, Hoon?
- No.
Don't be nervous.
(Seoul Jumbo Pork Cutlet and Hamburger Steak)
Does it show? No, I'm not nervous.
We kept labour costs the tightest.
Other teams used 2 part-timers each, but we used 1.
(200 dollars, 200 dollars)
(200 dollars)
If we save just 200 dollars each,
we start out 400 dollars ahead.
I think we're going to win.
We have to, having come all this way.
It's not overconfidence.
One of my restaurants is about this scale.
If we run around really fast, three people can pull it off.
It's a game I've played 365 times a year for years,
so three people are more than enough.
- Let's do this.
- Let's go.
- What we prepared this time is...
jumbo pork cutlet...
and hamburger steak with lasagna.
(Hamburger steak with lasagna, 17.90 dollars)
One, two, three. Gosh, what's that?
Isn't doing hamburger steak and pork cutlet...
too predictable?
I think Kim Hoon's team...
would not be picked much.
The menu was cliche.
(Chef's jumbo pork cutlet and hamburger steak with lasagna)
We've always cooked tailored to mass appeal, you know.
Tenderloin steak rice,
cream shrimp and sweet fried chicken,
prawn yakisoba,
jambon cream pasta,
lasagna cheese balls,
meat-packed kimchi stew, and spicy stir-fried pork.
We always make mass-appeal food.
This time, the theme is "Everyone's Restaurant," after all.
Pork cutlet and hamburger steak are dishes...
that have always been by our side.
I think we came up with the items with the least room for division.
(Competing in the finals with crowd-pleasing menus again)
(Hamburger steak sauce)
(However)
What is this burnt smell?
I smell something burning.
(What?)
(Sighing)
It's burnt.
I had a total mental breakdown back then.
This is the worst.
Let me taste it.
We can't use this.
- We can't use this.
- What do we do?
I tried it, and it had an unsalvageable burnt taste.
But we prepared...
just enough hamburger steak sauce for our use.
(Urgent measures need to be taken.)
(Teammate Kim Jong In assesses the situation.)
The thing that burned just now is the demi-glace sauce, right?
- Does the entire sauce taste burnt?
- Yes.
We have plenty of cream. Let's go with cream for the lasagna.
We have plenty of heavy cream and chilli oil for the lasagna.
Blend the shiitake mushrooms and put them in together.
There were certain ingredients we had plenty of left over.
What burned? Did the bottom burn?
- I think the bottom burnt.
- It's burnt.
If it smells, throw it out.
(Scraping the entire batch)
It's okay.
We needed to make a new sauce,
but we didn't have the ingredients.
We gathered all the heavy cream we had.
And I went to Team Son of Jeonju.
Could you spare and lend us any leftover minced garlic?
- We haven't started yet.
- Really?
- So we will give you three for now.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
I borrowed garlic from them.
I'm sorry, but if you have starch, could we get just a little?
Here you go.
We borrowed starch.
We had chilli oil, so we added spicy flavour with chilli oil.
We made a sauce using the ingredients on hand.
(A new hamburger steak sauce)
The sauce changed.
What we originally made was a demi-glace sauce,
but it changed to a cream mushroom sauce.
(Tasting the improvised sauce)
This is good. Well done.
- Is it over?
- It's done.
Let's make the lasagna together right away.
I brought out lasagna, which is my specialty.
I think that's the dish that made Kim Hoon who he is today.
(Lasagna sheet)
Layer lasagna,
rice, ragu sauce,
hamburger steak, and cream sauce...
in that order on a foil plate,
and bake for 7 to 10 minutes...
until the cheese turns golden brown.
And right from the start, when designing the menu,
we only composed it of dishes that could pick up speed.
Pork cutlet is cooked in a deep fryer,
and the soba is done once we boil the noodles and pour the broth over.
(They pour the broth and serve it right away.)
The hamburger steak is ready once we take it out of the oven.
We planned the dishes that Jong In could cook quickly.
It's 12:30pm now.
- I'll set up the dining hall.
- Go.
It's quite spacious.
Looking at other teams' menus and our price range,
I figured we had to compete on table turnover rate.
So I thought we should sweep up all the tables.
(Strategy: Increase tables to compete on turnover rate.)
First, I turned the 4-seater tables into 2-seater tables.
(Turning the 4-seater tables into 2-seater tables)
We were equally given 9 tables each,
but we separated them all.
Then we end up with about twice as many tables.
Five, six...
(Calculating something)
We need to buy them all.
We'll buy all six tables.
We'll buy everything you have.
(They bought extra tables for 120 dollars.)
Since we have three workers,
we're one person short compared to others.
Then when customers leave,
we might not be able to clean up immediately to seat the next ones,
so if we just have plenty of tables,
we can seat them at empty tables without having to clear them.
So we decided to lay out as many tables as possible.
(A turnover strategy taking on extra costs)
This is tough.
I bought up all the spare tables.
I got them all.
(Labour cost: Son of Jeonju, 400 dollars, Noodle Shop, 400 dollars,)
(Seoul Jumbo Pork Cutlet and Hamburger Steak, 200 dollars)
(Table: standard table, 40 dollars, bar table, 20 dollars)
(Son of Jeonju, 360 dollars, Noodle Shop, 460 dollars,)
(Seoul Jumbo Pork Cutlet and Hamburger Steak, 480 dollars)
Even while doing business in Seoul,
I always held pride in flavour...
as a chef from Jeonju.
(A course meal aiming for a high average spend per customer)
I wanted to put in...
all the know-how earned through blood and sweat...
to present dishes I could show with confidence.
No one in Korea who would dislike pork cutlet and hamburger steak.
They are dishes that have always been right by our side.
Without a doubt, we will take first place on this.
Let's do this.
This is the final. Let's have fun.
- Let's do this.
Let's try our best, Jong In.
Please.
- Tae Hee, prep our battle stations.
- Battle stations.
- This is the final.
Let's go!
We will now begin the finals,
Everyone's Restaurant.
(Everyone's Restaurant is open.)
We are going to win.
We're almost there.
This is the beginning.
In the final round, different target demographics...
will visit across time slots.
(Final Round, Everyone's Restaurant)
(Different target demographics visiting by time slot)
(Seniors, office workers, students, foreigners, restaurateurs, families)
The first group is restaurateurs.
- Darn it.
- Right from the start?
I'm scared.
We're starting with restaurateurs.
Gosh, we're in trouble.
(Sighing)
Restaurateurs from the start?
Give me some water.
In a way, it means pros are meeting pros.
Facing restaurateurs right from the start like this...
could kill our momentum if things go wrong.
(The first target that put all three teams on edge)
Stay calm.
(Restaurateurs)
(To be continued)
(Restaurateurs with an average of 23 years in the business)
(Multiple restaurant openings)
(Having iterated branding right up until recently)
(Restaurant industry veterans)
Can we head in?
I'm visiting Hanok Village for this.
I guess this is the place.
(The 32 participants of Street Restaurant Fighter)
This is it.
Something's really catching my eye.
What do you want to eat?
(They are visiting as customers today.)
This is triggering my PTSD.
They have brand new signs here.
So this is how it looks.
It's an actual restaurant.
(Kim Kwan Hoon: It's an actual restaurant.)
- This is bigger than I thought.
- Right.
It says "free" here.
It must be Kim Hoon.
- It's free. The freebies strategy.
- No more freebies.
- Stop with the freebies already.
- That's enough.
He always gives out free stuff.
This looks delicious.
Stop with the freebies already.
My goodness. Seok Cheon is here.
Seok Cheon is here.
The customers are here.
He always gives out free stuff.
(The calm before the storm inside the restaurant)
- My goodness.
- It's 2.9 dollars.
- What is? Buckwheat noodles?
- Cold buckwheat noodles.
- Oh, dear.
- It's 2.9 dollars.
- Unbelievable.
- It's only 2.9 dollars.
(Signboards emphasizing freebies and cheap side dishes)
The cold buckwheat noodles are only 2.9 dollars.
(Thanks to them, it's bustling in front of Kim Hoon's restaurant.)
They are making pork cutlet and hamburger steak.
Should I have a pork cutlet? What should I eat?
- "Chef-crafted..." - It sounds delicious.
(Reading carefully)
Calamari and shrimp fresh pasta.
(Menu posters on the exterior wall of Noodle Shop)
(Noodles crafted by the chef)
(Promotional copy for house-made noodles)
Calamari and shrimp fresh pasta does sound delicious.
The menu doesn't feel heavy somehow.
Right. It's a bit light, but it sounds like a gourmet treat.
There are so many menu items.
(Jung Ho Young's restaurant competes with diverse options.)
It looks delicious.
They have a lot of tempting items on the menu.
What does Son of Jeonju have on the menu?
- What? It's a 7-course meal?
- They serve a 7-course meal?
This is very tempting.
It's a course meal?
A course meal at 34 dollars?
- Do we get to eat all of them?
- Yes.
- It includes all of these.
- It includes seven dishes.
A course meal is oddly tempting.
This one has one menu item, and that one has a course meal.
- My goodness.
- It's amazing.
Where on earth should we go?
What do I do? Where am I supposed to go?
- What do I do?
- Can't we just eat everything?
What should we eat?
Did you decide?
(What will be the restaurateurs' first choice?)
My gosh. They've made up their minds.
- Really?
- They made a choice.
(The restaurant chosen by Team Kim Ho Yoon)
Hello.
Can we eat now? Hello.
Hello. We're two.
(Lee Sung Hoon)
- Hello.
- We will take a seat inside.
- Please start from the inside.
- Please make it delicious.
- Okay.
I was surprised to see them.
Let's go.
(Teams Edward Kwon and Kim Kwan Hoon also chose Lee Sung Hoon.)
- Hello.
- The chefs are coming.
(Kwak Dong Hoon and Song Ji Beom, Kim Hee Eun and Yoon Dae Hyun)
You're the third.
(Hong Seok Cheon and Park Min Hyuk)
More people are coming.
(Shin Ga Young and Lim Hong Geun)
That makes eight teams.
(8 out of the 16 teams have entered.)
This restaurant has so many people.
- So many people showed up here.
- People are crowding in here.
That's true.
The chefs who do course meals all came here out of curiosity.
That's right.
The fine-dining chefs are all here.
This is number one among the chefs.
Especially for chefs like us who offer course meals,
- we'd want to visit here.
- Exactly.
- You're right.
- Rather than the single dishes.
And the other menus are a bit predictable. They're common.
- I do want to try this.
- Right.
That's my favourite.
But I want to check this place out.
- I want to see the course.
- I want to experience it.
We need to experience the things we're curious about.
I'm very curious about the execution.
This means they can actually deliver the service just as it is.
I can see why chefs would be drawn to this restaurant.
The lineup looks solid.
The service score counts too, right?
(Things will be evaluated even more strictly.)
(Cumulative customers)
(Lee Sung Hoon's restaurant has twice as many customers.)
All the chefs came over here.
Okay.
(Nervous)
We need to start on the beef tartare now, right?
It's 4, 4, 2, and then 2, 2, 2 portions.
(16 portions right from the start)
(The 1st dish of the 7-course meal)
(Beef tartare and seaweed bugak)
It doesn't need to be heavy in flavour.
(A French-style tartare to lightly whet the appetite)
- Seaweed bugak.
- Seaweed bugak and sorrel.
(Finished with a Korean touch using seaweed bugak)
- Thank you.
It deserves a perfect score.
Is this for 1 person or 2?
I guess it's for two to share.
(Course 1: Shared for 2, beef tartare and seaweed bugak)
Can I get extra small plates?
Extra plates? Please wait a moment.
Go ahead and eat.
Thank you.
(She brings out small plates right away.)
You should set out the extra plates beforehand.
- I should? Okay, thank you.
- They all would need one.
- Okay.
- Everyone needs one.
(The part-timer takes in feedback immediately.)
She's setting them out.
The seasoning is a bit strong.
- Really?
- It is strong for me.
I like rich, intense flavours.
I only eat tteokbokki with strong seasoning.
Really?
(Only tteokbokki is special to me.)
It's slightly spicy.
- Yes. What is this spicy kick?
- What is it?
There's diced jalapeno in here.
The spicy kick is from the jalapeno.
They minced jalapeno and put it in.
- Jalapeno and caper.
- I think it's jalapeno.
I want to have some makgeolli.
Me too.
- It'd go well with alcohol.
- Some makgeolli would be nice.
The seasoning on this is meant for bar snacks.
I think so.
It's spicy.
(The second course dish to follow right after)
(The 2nd dish of the 7-course meal)
(Menchi katsu and squid ink ciabatta)
Should I put the menchi katsu in?
Yes.
(Minced pork cutlet, menchi katsu)
(The 2nd dish is warm deep-fried dish.)
(Planning to rev up the appetite with greasy fried food)
I took out the menchi katsu.
Ciabatta.
(To be served alongside sweet mayo sauce and ciabatta)
Tae Hee, sprinkle the cheese just a bit more generously.
Okay.
(Preparing cheese and accompaniments with a Western feel)
(The 2nd dish: Menchi katsu and squid ink ciabatta)
Here is the second dish.
This is pretty.
(Dipping straight into the sauce for a bite)
- They should have it prepared.
- The sauce is good.
I love the sauce.
(Trying the sauce immediately)
This is exceeding my expectations.
(Impressed)
(Dipping deep into the sauce)
They cook well.
The sauce has acidity,
so it isn't heavy and tastes great.
This place is good.
I'll expect even more.
This is good enough.
I like it.
(Exclaiming)
They really fry well here.
(A tendon master)
- The fried food is good.
- It's delicious.
(Everyone's praising the deep-fry.)
This also has a spicy kick.
Is this it for the menchi katsu orders?
- We have one more dish to serve.
- Okay.
(Cool makguksu)
(Lee Sung Hoon's perilla oil makguksu)
(Fusion makguksu featuring chilled buckwheat noodles...)
(paired with peanut soba sauce, tomatoes, and perilla leaf pesto)
Peanut sauce over noodles, and tomatoes?
- That's it.
- Okay.
(The exotic umami of peanut butter)
Good. That's enough.
(Perilla leaf pesto)
(Adding nutty aroma with perilla leaf oil)
Two or three drops of perilla oil.
(For cleansing the palate right before the main dish)
Perilla oil makguksu?
I guess customers will like it.
- The feel...
- This is refreshing.
Is this perilla oil?
This is perilla oil makguksu.
- The peanut butter is delicious.
- It feels a bit...
- like an homage to mazesoba.
- Exactly.
- Actually...
- This is good.
I thought the combination was a little odd,
but this is good. It's multifaceted.
(Edward Kwon takes a bite too.)
(He tries it again right away.)
(Done)
Honestly speaking, for a course meal like this,
this noodle portion is way too big.
- It's too big.
- I agree.
Because as you head further back, it starts getting heavier.
You just need to take two bites and clear out.
- Exactly.
- When it tastes just good.
Still, customers might like it because the portions are generous.
That's true.
Selling like this, they won't have any margins left.
What do you think? The makguksu. Do you like it?
- It's good.
- Is it good?
(Meanwhile, Jung Ho Young and Song Hoon)
Are you open for business?
(Relieved)
- Are you open?
- Yes.
Hello.
- Long time no see.
(Kim Mi Ryeong and Lee Jun Seong)
- Hello.
- Congratulations.
Why don't you take a look first?
And have a seat anywhere you want.
I'm sorry, but I can't be outside.
Can you close the door for me?
(Right.)
(The participant can't leave the restaurant.)
(Accumulative customers: 8)
(The customers start reading at the menu.)
The abalone risotto sounds good.
I think I can finish everything.
Then...
Since I want something cool...
But I also want pasta. This looks good.
That looks good. Everything looks good.
- First...
- Let's try it first,
- Yes.
- and we'll see...
- Let's just have it.
- Or we can...
- One, two, three, four.
- One, two...
(We prepared everything for people who can't decide.)
- Let's try everything.
(Perfect aim)
- Are you ready to order?
- We're ready.
We'll get one combo,
one mianbao xia,
one risotto,
- Yes.
- one pasta and one shaved ice.
Two sushi and one pasta.
- Two sushi?
- Yes.
And one pasta.
- One combo and...
- Okay.
shaved ice, please.
We'll get this combo,
- pasta, - Okay.
and shaved ice.
- That's perfect.
- Okay.
What's so perfect?
We got an order.
- Two sushi.
- One pasta and two sushi.
Two sushi.
- Two sushi combo.
- Two sushi.
(The Noodle Shop's another weapon)
(Sushi)
I prepared salmon,
(Salmon)
halibut,
and tuna back.
(Tuna back)
(Hyungjae assorted sushi, 24 dollars)
- It's here.
- About 65 percent of the price...
is the ingredient cost.
That's...
- It's good.
- Good, right?
We cut it fresh.
It tastes like sushi from a sushi restaurant.
- This is a sushi restaurant.
- Right.
There's a sushi chef inside.
- He didn't press rice hard.
- No.
It scatters in my mouth.
- Does it taste like Japan?
- It's so good.
- This is so good.
- You know I love sushi.
- As a sushi maniac...
- You love sushi.
The salmon tastes so good.
The fish tastes so good.
The sushi is the best.
Two cold udon, right?
(Washing udon noodles)
(In the udon noodles,)
(pour the cold broth to complete it.)
(Cold handmade udon and deep-fried shrimp for 14.50 dollars)
One by one.
That's so big.
Look at the size of the bowl.
It's a lot.
Isn't this from...
Chef Jung Ho Young's restaurant?
- Yes. From his own restaurant.
- Yes.
(He brought the bowls from his restaurant.)
(The noodle expert Mi Ryeong tries it.)
(Exclaiming)
The noodles are perfect.
The noodles are so good.
- The noodles are really good.
- This is really good.
Are these the same noodles he uses in his restaurant?
No, that place uses...
thick udon noodles.
You use thicker noodles...
- in your restaurant.
- Yes, but here...
Did you make noodles for this?
I'm using thin noodles, so it's easier to boil them.
- I see.
- I like it.
I made them in my restaurant.
You made them?
There's something I learned from the survival competition.
Instead of pork cutlet,
- people would prefer pasta or udon.
- Something new.
Yes, something they didn't try before.
Three items and four items.
It's a course.
(The pork cutlet restaurant is slower than other restaurants.)
(Grunting)
Their menu isn't strong enough.
Right? Compared to other places...
It's not something I want to try in Jeonju.
No.
(Between a 7-course meal...)
(and a flashy combination of Japanese and Western noodles)
- The other places are too strong.
- This is kind of boring.
- Where do you want to go?
- Let's go here.
We know what it tastes like,
but that's more tempting.
- Are you open?
- Hello.
- Yes, we're open. Come on in.
- Min.
Welcome.
Hello.
Have a seat.
- Here's the menu.
- Hurry up and take our order.
You don't have time to clean it up.
- I'll have cheese.
- You need to check it.
- Where is it?
- Yes.
(The special order sheet...)
(only in Seoul Jumbo Pork Cutlet and Hamburger Steak)
(Look at the menu and the pictures.)
(Order here)
(The combos come with a cold buckwheat noodles.)
(Write the quantity.)
Get one cold buckwheat noodle.
Cold buckwheat noodles. Cheese.
Is that enough?
(While choosing the menu in the order sheet...)
Hello.
(Yang Ji Sam and Go Min Seong)
Do you want to move to a bigger table?
- Hello.
- I'll have pork cutlet.
- Pork cutlet?
- Yes.
- Have a seat.
Hello.
- You're amazing.
- Thank you.
(Yoo Bang Nyeong and Yoo Sang Min)
Thank you for ordering.
Help yourselves with water and drinks.
Thank you.
What's this?
It's soda.
What do we need for the self-service bar?
Can you tell me again?
- Wet wipes.
- Okay.
- Cutlery.
- Tissues.
- Okay.
- And cups.
- Yes.
(Easy self-service bar)
(For spoons, forks, knives, wet wipes, and plates)
(Free unlimited drinks)
(The customers can grab what they need...)
(from the self-service bar.)
You have a customer.
Hello. If you grab a seat,
I'll bring you the menu.
Are there still people hesitating outside?
- We're the last ones.
- Everyone's gone.
(Everyone has entered.)
The CEO of Cheonggiwa Town...
- Are they here together?
- Yes. As a team.
- We should greet them.
- It's overwhelming.
(Punching)
Hello.
(Getting sentimental to see those he worked with)
- You can do it.
- We can do it.
Put it here.
It's overwhelming to see them again, right?
(He suddenly can't stop crying.)
What?
You're funny.
(At that moment, they receive their first order.)
- Is it an order?
- Yes.
(There's no time to cry.)
What? Are they having all three?
We have three orders.
Okay.
Serving two fried rice first.
(Finishing up with handmade garlic flakes)
(Glancing)
The fried rice looks good.
The shrimp is slightly deep fried.
Should we order one?
Sure.
- And three hamburger steaks?
- Yes.
(Just grab the hamburger steak from the food warmer.)
- It's three hamburgers, isn't it?
- Three.
- Is the pork cutlet ready?
- I have two ready.
(Finish it up with plenty of handmade sauce.)
- Perfect.
- Thank you.
(Serving the dishes quickly as they planned)
- Your pork cutlet is here.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
Here's your handmade jumbo pork cutlet. Enjoy.
Here's your hamburger steak.
- Thank you.
- There's ragu and nurungji below.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
(All served in no time)
I'm embarrassed to present fried rice to you.
This is very good.
It's salt fried rice. It's kind of salty.
- That's right.
- I like it.
I used salt and bacon grease.
- Thank you.
That's a lot.
Is it demi-glace?
(Nodding)
I like the sauce.
- Right? It's good.
- Yes.
Next 20 people are restaurant owners...
- in Jeonju.
- What? There are more?
What did she just say?
Restaurant owners in Jeonju.
- Okay.
- Twenty of them.
Okay.
My goodness.
More people are coming.
What matters the most is the commercial zone.
We need to see if it's worth paying...
for this short event.
(Average of 12 years of business experience in Jeonju)
(They have clear standards for food business.)
Are we eating in there?
(25 food business owners in Jeonju)
- Are we going in there?
- Yes, we're eating inside.
Can we go in?
I think so.
- Do you want to check it out?
- Shall we?
(Kim Hoon's waiting for new customers.)
Food business in Jeonju?
(But no matter how long they wait...)
Okay.
(No customers are entering.)
Open the door and see if there's a line.
(Checking outside)
No?
(Empty)
- There's one.
- What?
There's one person.
One?
(The restaurant owners entered another restaurant.)
(Only one team is waiting.)
This place is packed.
(Lee Sung Hoon's restaurant)
(Jung Ho Young's restaurant)
(And...)
(Kim Hoon's restaurant is empty.)
For real?
Why is that?
(Kim Hoon is trying to figure out what's going on.)
They want something more special than a pork cutlet.
A special dish.
Restaurant owners are...
- familiar with pork cutlets.
- That's right.
It seems everyone's going to the restaurants on each side.
No one's going there.
- Because the menu is too ordinary.
- Too ordinary?
It's not something they'd want to try here.
(To be continued)
That means no one chose us.
(The number of cumulative customers)
(33 for Lee Sung Hoon, 16 for Jung Ho Young)
(8 for Kim Hoon)
(This is chaos.)
(If we can't do it, we're through.)
(I want to pull it off.)
- Come here.
- The next target is...
(The elders)
(Elders, foreigners, university students, office workers)
(Family)
(They must meet everyone's taste.)
(The customer ratings are updated in real time.)
(The customer ratings upset me.)
(This field is all about the customer ratings.)
(1 customer rating)
(Right now, the 1st place goes to...)
This is nerve-racking.
(The end of the fierce restaurant battle)
(I'm desperate to place 1st.)
(I will be the winner.)
(I'm here to win.)
(Who will win the trophy?)